When the cheering stopped, there were... Eight Men Out.
Eight Men Out is a drama, history film directed by John Sayles.
Buck Weaver and Hap Felsch are young idealistic players on the Chicago White Sox, a pennant-winning team owned by Charles
Comiskey -  a penny-pinching, hands-on manager who underpays his players and treats them with disdain.
And when gamblers and hustlers discover that Comiskey's demoralized players are ripe for a
money-making scheme, one by one the team members agree to throw the World Series.
But when the White Sox are defeated, a couple of sports writers smell a fix and a
national scandal explodes, ripping the cover off America's favorite pastime.
Buck Weaver, played by John Cusack.
Charles Comiskey, played by Clifton James.
Arnold Rothstein, played by Michael Lerner.
Bill Burns, played by Christopher Lloyd.
Kid Gleason, played by John Mahoney.
Hap Felsch, played by Charlie Sheen.
Eight Men Out is a 1988 American period sports drama film based on Eliot Asinof's
1963 book Eight Men Out: The Black Sox and the 1919 World Series.
It was written and directed by John Sayles.
The film is a dramatization of Major League Baseball's Black Sox Scandal in which eight members
of the Chicago White Sox conspired with gamblers to lose the 1919 World Series.
Most of the movie was filmed at Bush Stadium in Indianapolis, Indiana.
The film explores themes of sports, baseball, historical figure.
The tone is emotional.